thegunsource.com 2011-11-03

# TheGunSource: privacy

**Privacy Notice**

TGSCOM, Inc. (herein called “We, Us, Our, Company”) respects your (herein called “You, Your, Customer”) concerns about privacy and values the trust you have placed in us. This Privacy Notice describes the types of personal information we collect, how we may use that information, and with whom we may share it. Our Privacy Notice also describes the measures we take to ensure the security of the information provided to us. In addition, we note the choices you can make about how we use the information you provide to us. Our contact information is provided at the end of this document, should you need to reach us to update your contact information, remove your information from our mailing lists, or if you have any questions about our privacy practices. 

This online Privacy Notice applies only to information collected by TGSCOM, Inc. through electronic means, such as, but not limited to, our websites, and may not apply to information collected offline. This Privacy Notice does not apply to any third-party websites not owned and/or operated by TGSCOM, Inc.

_**Information we collect and how we use it:**_

We collect and use information about you to communicate with you about our products, services, and/or promotions. We also collect information to improve the shopping experience of TGSCOM, Inc. consumers. The following explains the ways we obtain information about you, the types of information we obtain, and how we use this information:

**Electronic Mail**

When you subscribe to our e-mail newsletter list, you provide us your email address so we may communicate with you via e-mail. We will send you e-mail only if you have provided us with your e-mail address and have asked us to communicate with you via this method. 

**Purchases**

When you place an order or purchase a product, you may be required to provide us with contact information and payment information (such as credit card information) so that we may process your order. When your payment method is a credit or debit card, we use your credit/debit card information only to process and fulfill your order.

**Contests, Promotions, and Surveys**

When you provide your personal contact information to enter a contest we may use this information to administer said contest and contact you regarding your entry. In addition, we may collect personal information in order to administer promotions, surveys, or other site features. The information provided by you will be subject to any and all privacy practices explained in this Privacy Notice.

**Customer Support**

If you contact one of our Customer Support Team Members, we may ask you for information such as your name, address, telephone number, and email address so we can respond to your questions or comments. With your consent, we may retain this information to personalize your experience with us and better assist you the next time you contact us.

**Cookies**

A “cookie” is a small file containing a string of characters that is sent to your computer when you visit a website. When you visit the website again, the cookie allows that site to recognize your browser. Cookies may store user preferences and other information. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some website features or services may not function properly without cookies. TGSCOM, Inc. operated websites use cookies to remember your preferences. We may also use cookies to provide services and advertising more relevant to your interests.

**IP Address**

Like most websites, our servers automatically record the page requests made when you visit TGSCOM, Inc. operated websites. These server logs typically include your web request, Internet Protocol address (IP address), browser type, browser language, and the date and time of your request. Your IP address may be used within TGSCOM Inc. as necessary for reporting and other purposes such as, but not limited to, fraud detection and prevention.

TGSCOM, Inc. only processes personal information for the purposes described in this Privacy Notice and/or the supplementary privacy notices for specific services. Such supplemental privacy notices will be made available publicly, if applicable.

**_**  
Information Sharing:**_**

TGSCOM, Inc. does not rent, share, or sell personal information (whether public or private) about its consumers with any third parties. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our websites, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to use this information only as necessary to perform these services on our behalf and keep this information confidential unless otherwise required by law. We may share this information within the TGSCOM, Inc. company for business purposes. We may also disclose information about you to comply with legal requirements. 

We reserve the right to transfer any information about you in the event of the sale or transfer of all or a portion of our business or assets. If the business is transferred, we will provide you with the opportunity to tell us that you would prefer that information about you not be transferred. Should such a transfer occur, we will use reasonable efforts to attempt to ensure that the transferee uses personal information about you in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Notice.

**_**Information Security:**_**

The security of personal information is a high priority. We maintain administrative, technical, and physical safeguards to protect against unauthorized disclosure, use, alteration, and/or destruction of the personal information in our possession. We are committed to providing appropriate security controls to protect personal information we store against foreseeable hazards.

**_**Third Party Links:**_**

TGSCOM, Inc. websites may contain links to other websites that operate independently of TGSCOM, Inc. and are not under our control. We provide links to other websites solely for your convenience and information. Other websites may have their own privacy notices, which we suggest you review if you visit any of these third-party websites. TGSCOM, Inc. is not responsible for information that is provided by, or collected through, those websites or for any other use of those websites.

**_Your Choices_ :**

If you prefer not to receive product information or promotions from us, please contact us using one of the options provided below to request that your information be removed from our records. To unsubscribe from e-mail newsletter mailings please use the “Unsubscribe” link within the e-mail message.

You may request that we update or correct the personal information about you that we currently have on file.

You may choose to set your browser to not accept cookies from our websites. Please see “Cookies” for further information.

When you provide us with your personal information to complete a purchase or another type of transaction or request, we will use this information to perform this task. If we use this information in a manner other than the purpose for which it was collected, then we will ask for your consent prior to such use. This is subject to our “Terms & Conditions”.

You may choose to opt-out of our e-mail newsletter mailing list during the order checkout process on our websites.

_**Your Consent:**_

By using any TGSCOM, Inc. operated website, you consent to our privacy practices as described in this Privacy Notice.

_**Terms and Conditions:**_

**_Contact Us:_**

If you would like to reach us in order to update your contact information, remove your name from our mailing list, or if have any questions about TGSCOM, Inc. privacy practices please contact us [here](https://securecheckout.tgscom.com/Contact.aspx?sid=2) or call 1-800-518-3808. You may also write to us at:

TGSCOM, Inc.  
Attn: Privacy Matters  
1449 S. Broadway Street  
Green Bay, WI 54304  
Fax: 920-569-4252

We will respond to your inquiry or investigate your concern as quickly as possible. 

This document is subject to change without notice. The most current copy of our Privacy Notice will always be available at this page.

Effective date: May 2006 - Last modified May 2010
